Nattell, Tom; Papers apap191
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Thomas Nattell Papers
1956-2002
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap191
12.1 cubic ft.
The Thomas Nattell papers document the life of a mental health worker and political activist active during the 1980s and 1990s in Albany, New York. He created and participated in organizations like the Albany Peace and Energy Council (APEC) and the Three Guys From Albany poetry troupe. He also acted as promoter and event coordinator for movie showings, poetry open mics and an annual 24-hour poetry reading alongside a coinciding international postcard art event. Nattell used poetry and other arts to advance world peace, anti-nuclear power and proliferation, and environmental issues. This collection contains videos of events, photographs, scrapbooks full of art and poetry mailed from around the world to Nattell, subject files with research on topics related to his professional work as well as his activism, poetry, correspondence, and clippings.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted. Please note there is material containing adult content in Series 1.
Acquisition Information
Thomas Nattell donated the records in January of 2005.
Biographical Sketch
Thomas "Tom" Cole Nattell was born in 1950. He lived his life entirely in Albany, New York aside from a short period during his childhood. He received a B.A. in Anthropology in 1974, a M.A. in Anthropology in 1976 and a M.S.W. in 1979 all from the State University of New York at Albany. He worked as a research associate for the New York State Council on Children and Families and other positions until settling in 1988 at the New York State Office of Mental Health (NYS OMH) as a program coordinator and as a Research Scientist III until the end of his life.
Nattell was widely known as a poet and environmentalist. His activism dates back to the 1960s, when he started a sit-in at Albany High School gymnasium demanding a Black Studies program. He used poetry and protest gatherings to support issues including AIDS awareness, environmentalism, anti-nuclear proliferation, Native American rights and pacifism. He was a member of many organizations apart from his work at the NYS OMH. Nattell was a founding member of the Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance (CDANA) which later became the Albany Peace and Energy Council (APEC), a member of the poetry group "Three Guys from Albany," a promoter and events coordinator for performances by the Bread and Puppet Circus. Nattell promoted other events, including readings at the New York State Writers Institute, and founded Open Mic poetry nights at the now-closed QE2 club on Central Avenue in Albany, New York. He created an annual 24-hour poetry reading and APEC fund-raiser that occurred for a decade called the "Readings Against the End of the World" (RAEW). Nattell authored many letters to the editor and was a frequent commentator on local issues in regional newspapers like the Albany Times Union and the Knickerbocker News, and eventually wrote his own column called "The Simple Life" in the alternative news weekly magazine Metroland.
Nattell died at age 52 in 2005 of throat cancer, survived by his long time friend and partner Mary Anne Winslow, a son and daughter and two brothers.
Source: Grondahl, Paul. "Rebel poet nears final stanza." Albany Times Union. 16 January 2005.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains videos of events, photographs, scrapbooks full of art and poetry mailed from around the world to Nattell for display during events, subject files with research on topics related to his professional work as well as his activism, poetry, correspondence with politicians, business owners and poets, resumes, magazines, promotional material, and more. While Nattell was widely known as a poet, only a few samples of his poetry are present in the collection: "Hiroshima" and the "Columbus Day fantasies". This collection provides insight into day-to-day life of a mental health coordinator, event organization in Albany, activism and event coverage in the media, and the early "green" environmentalist movement. It features correspondence with prominent individuals such as poets Allen Ginsberg and Anne Waldman, as well as Albany Mayor Thomas M Whalen III. The collection also contains information on CDANA/APEC, a small 501 (c) council with many official newsletters and press releases regarding environmental and political causes.
Please note that dates reflect date of use where possible or date of publication. Not all dates are inclusive.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Events, 1974-2002, Undated. 7.3 cubic ft.
Series 2 - Biographical, 1956-1995, Undated. 2.05 cubic ft.
Series 3 - Capital District Anti-Nuclear Association, Albany Peace and Energy Council, 1979-1992, Undated. .5 cubic ft.
Series 4 - Subject Files, 1967-1998, Undated. 2.25 cubic ft.
Series 1 is arranged alphabetically. In the case of duplicate titles, chronological order is also used. Series 2 is arranged alphabetically, and in the case of duplicate titles, chronologically. Series 3 is arranged chronologically. Series 4 is arranged alphabetically.
Social Activists and Public Advocates; Literature; Conservation and the Environment; Art; Albany, New York; Environmentalism.; Environmentalism--New York (State)--New York.; Cold War in popular culture.; Cold War--Poetry.; Cold War--Press coverage--United States.; Poetry.; Poetry--Beat.; Poetry--20th century.; Nuclear warfare.; Nuclear nonproliferation.; AIDS (Disease)--New York (State)--New York--Prevention.; Community theater.; Community Support Services.; Albany County (N.Y.); Clippings; Press Releases; Correspondence; Files by subject; Black-and-White Negatives; Notes; VHS (TM); Galley proofs; Stickers; Postcards; Magazines (periodicals); Fanzines; Newsletters; Photographs; Scrapbooks; journals (periodicals); Nattell, Thomas Cole, 1950-2002.; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-1997.; Waldman, Anne, 1945- .; Whalen III, Thomas M., 1934-2002.; Golub, Neil.; Atwood, Margaret, 1939- .; Sherman, Margot Lee.; Schumann, Peter, 1934- .; Bread and Puppet Theater.; Capital District Anti-Nuclear Association; Albany Peace and Energy Council; Coalition to Keep Albany's Name Nuclear Free.; New York State Writers Institute.; State University of New York at Albany.; State University of New York at Albany. School of Social Welfare.; Price Chopper Corporation.; New York (State). Office of Mental Health.; New York (State). Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities.
- Events, 1974-2002; Undated; 1; 7.3 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains documents related to events in the Albany, New York region. It contains correspondence, photographs, negatives, promotional materials, press clippings, fliers and posters, poems, newsletters, and handwritten notes. Notable groups, institutions and individuals mentioned in this series include: Allen Ginsberg, Anne Waldman, the Bread and Puppet Circus, the New York State Writers Institute, the Hudson Valley Writers Guild and the 10-year annual event Readings Against the End of the World (RAEW). Nattell was involved in the creation, promotion and coordination of most of these events. Oversized materials in this series include scrapbooks which hold assorted art and poems that were mailed in and displayed ca. 1980-1995. Also included are scrapbooks containing photographs of readers at the Readings Against the End of the World.
  - Albany Arts Decentralization/Albany People's Poetry: clippings, applications, galleys, 1987 September 23-1989 May (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 1)
  - Albany First Night: map, magazine, 1994 December 25; 1995 December 24; 1996 December 29; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany People's Poetry: photos, fliers, correspondence, 1982 November 23-1988 March 15; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 2)
  - Albany People's Poetry: press releases, flyer, Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 3)
  - American Playhouse, TS Eliott, "In America", 1989 June (Drawer E3, Video-tape 1)
  - Amnesty International (Albany Chapter): correspondence, 1987 November 11-1988/1989 Winter (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 4)
  - Amnesty International rally against the death penalty, 1989 May 13 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 2)
  - Assorted Events: Anne Waldman, Open Mic for Poets, "Huitzika", "Brigadistas", "The Door": posters, clippings, 1985 May-1996 November 11; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Events including Maurice Kenney: fliers, clippings, 1983-1984; 1990; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 5)
  - Assorted Events: fliers, brochures, clippings, 1993 February 14; 1993 August (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 6)
  - Assorted Events including Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Tom's Trash, Earth Day 1995: fliers, photocopies, Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 7)
  - "The Atomic Café" film showing: promotional material, 1982 March 15-1982 July 07; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 8)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "Columbus: The New World Order": clippings, playbill, 1981 March 01; 1991 April 18; 1991 April 15; 1991 Spring (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 9)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "Columbus Trilogy": clippings, contracts, sheet music, 1983 November-1991 April 01; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 10)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "The Door": correspondence, clippings, 1984 November 12; 1985 May 17; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 11)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "The End Falls before the Beginning": promotional material, correspondence, news clippings, 1979 November 04-1993 August 09; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 12)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "The End Falls before the Beginning" "Travelling Circus": clippings, correspondence, 1983 September 02-1993 September 16; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 13)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "Fly or Die": clippings, photos, 1988 March 17-1994 May 05; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 14)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "Hunger of the Hungry": correspondence, promotional material, clippings, 1986 May 14-1986 September 06; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 15)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater/ Margo Lee Sherman play: clippings, photos, correspondence, 1974 July 04-1984 May 23; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 16)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "Our Domestic Circus 1989" event schedule, Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 17)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater: clippings, contact information, 1987 August 03-1988 March 17; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 18)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater "The Same Boat: the Passion of Chico Mendes": photos, press releases, music, 1983 July-1989 August 27; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 19)
  - Bread and Puppet Theater: photographs, Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 20)
  - "Brigadista" play: promotional material, contracts, correspondence, 1990 March 28-1991 September; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 21)
  - Columbus Day Rallies: press releases, fliers, clippings, 1992 August 04-1992 October 14; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 22)
  - Community Poetry Grant and Capital District Arts Decentralization: application, tax forms, fliers, 1988 April 08-1989 October 01; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 23)
  - Community Voice Event: galley proofs, Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 24)
  - Community Voice Reading Series: correspondence, photos, clippings, 1991 July 02-1993 September 01 (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence regarding events: RAEW, Poets in the Park, Peace Post, 1986 February 20-1993 March 02; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 26)
  - "Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power" film distributor's packet, 1986 September 24-1987 March; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 27)
  - "Disarming Images: Art for Nuclear Disarmament": art installation, letter cancelling Bread and Puppet performance, 1985 May 20; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 28)
  - Downtown Underground News Television Show: press releases, news clippings, 1989 February 20; 1989 February 09; 1989 November 24; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 29)
  - Downtown Underground News #2: Peace Post, Everydog, golf course, USS Albany, Babysphere, Infinity Road, Anne Waldman, 29 minutes, 1989 December (Drawer E3, Video-tape 3)
  - DUN 1 (Downtown Underground News #1), 1989 January (Drawer E3, Video-tape 4)
  - Earth Day 1995: clippings, fliers, correspondence, 1995 January 10; 1995 February 06; 1995 March 08; 1995 March 10 (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 30)
  - Earth Post, RAEW: fliers, schedules, galley proofs, 1986-1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 31)
  - Earth Poems: poems hung on display, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 32)
  - Earth Poems: poems hung on display, 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 33)
  - Earth Poems: scrapbook, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 2)
  - Earth Poems: submission request, clippings, 1994 May 27; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 34)
  - Earth Post 1991: clippings, mailing list, 1990 March 15-1990 May 27; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 35)
  - Earth Post: scrapbook 1, Undated (Box 8 (1-Events), Folder 1)
  - Earth Post: scrapbook 2, Undated (Box 8 (1-Events), Folder 2)
  - Earth Post: scrapbook 3, Undated (Box 9 (1-Events), Folder 3)
  - Earth Post: scrapbook 4, Undated (Box 9 (1-Events), Folder 4)
  - Ed Sanders reading and book signing at the QE2, 1995: clippings, 1995 April (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 36)
  - The 8th Anniversary Poetry open mic at QE2, 1995 March (Drawer E3, Video-tape 6)
  - Festival of the Arts for Peace: meeting minutes, news clippings, budget, 1980 December 03-1982 December 23 (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 38)
  - Festival of the Arts for Peace 1983: schedule, press releases, notes, 1982 September 23-1983 May 17; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 39)
  - First Night: correspondence, guides, promotional materials, 1988 December 31-1996 November 16; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 40)
  - Floor plans for venues: Halfmoon Café, QE2, Page Hall, etc, Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 41)
  - "From Hitler to M-X" promotional photography and materials, Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 42)
  - "Gangsters" play by Maishe Maponya at Page Hall: clippings, correspondence, fliers, 1984 December 07-1986 November 14; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 43)
  - General Electric Philmont original footage, 1987 August 15 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 5)
  - Ginsberg, Allen: posters, clippings, 1990 November 29-1990 December 26; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Ginsberg, Allen readings at the QE2, Writers Institute: correspondence, news clippings, 1986 February 01-1990 December 20; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 44)
  - Ginsberg, Allen and Janine Vega, QE2 benefit, 1990 November (Drawer E3, Video-tape 7)
  - Golf course Nattell, 1988 May 30 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 8)
  - Golf course Nattell, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 9)
  - Ground Zero Week: correspondence, schedules, press materials, 1982 February 18-1982 May 25; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 45)
  - Ground Zero Week: clippings, 1982 April 09-1982 April 26 (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 46)
  - Ground Zero Week, The Nuclear Nightmare of Children: posters, 1982 April 18; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Hiroshima-Nagasaki Anniversary: press releases, clippings, schedules, 1987 August 07-1995 August 07 (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 47)
  - Holman, Bob: portfolio, photographs, negatives, writing samples, 1991 November; 1995 June 19; 1996 August; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 48)
  - Horowitz, Mikhail: clippings, photographs, correspondence, 1985 April 11-1991 May (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 49)
  - Hudson Valley Writers Guild: correspondence, newsletters, press releases, 1988 February-1988 March; 1991 July-1991 August (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 50)
  - Huitzika: press releases, photographs, fliers, clippings, notes, 1987 February 10-1987 November 12; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 51)
  - Hudson Valley Writers Guild censorship meeting, Market Theater, Christine Miles, Les Urtouch, Paul Weinman, Mark Mischler, Judy Johnson, Peter Clough, 1989 November 05 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 10)
  - Illegible title, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 11)
  - Indigenous Day march and rally, Meldnic Printop Hope Albany, NY, 1992 October 12 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 12)
  - "In our Hands" film showing, 1983: press releases, correspondence, clippings, 1983 July 03-1983 December 12; Undated (Box 1 (1-Events), Folder 52)
  - International Mail Art Exhibit (Peaceworks): submissions. Contains adult material., 1988 May 21-1995 October 24; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 1)
  - Late PM tick- Rothenberg, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 13)
  - Love canal rally, Capitol-gov. mansion, 1989 September 15 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 14)
  - "Love thy Neighborhood convention": schedule, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 2)
  - Lundz, Diane early bm, wandering shots 1987 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 15)
  - "A Matter of Struggle," film showing: press releases, correspondence, clippings, poster, 1983 April 13-1986 June 03; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 3)
  - Newport News, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 16)
  - Newspaper clippings about events, 1984 April 23-1994 April 21 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 4)
  - Ninth Street theater: correspondence, press releases, 1989 December 26; 1990 May 28 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 5)
  - "Nuclear Capital District" talk by Nattell: APEC newsletters, notes, galley proofs, projections, clippings, 1986 Summer; 1987 Summer (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 6)
  - Ollie North Day, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 17)
  - "Ollie North Day" and "Brian Wilson and the Death Train": video presentation: flyer, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 7)
  - Open Mic for Poets: fliers, press releases, photographs, 1997 April 28-1997 April 30; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 8)
  - Peace Post, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 18)
  - Peace Post II, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 19)
  - Peace Post master, Undated (Drawer E3, Video-tape 20)
  - Peace Post: press release, names and addresses, 1992 February 29; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 9)
  - Peace Post: press release, notebook, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 10)
  - Peaceworks galleys and events: correspondence, press releases, reports, administrative documents, 1983 October 27-1990 October 30; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 11)
  - Photocopied photographs, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 12)
  - Poets in the Park 1998: poster, clippings, 1998 July 09; 1998 July 10; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Poets Action against AIDS: posters, clippings, contact lists, 1980 November 26-1998 November 29; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 13)
  - Poets in the Park: grant application, budget lists, 501 (c), 1982 November 23-1990 November 20; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 14)
  - Poets in the Park and other poetry events: press releases, 501 (c) forms, correspondence, 1986 May 02-1990 September 28; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 15)
  - Poetry Motel Foundation: grant application 1998, resume, clippings, correspondence, 1986 May 26-1997 September 11; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 16)
  - Poets in the Park: photos, correspondence, press releases, permit application, posters, 1990 July 18-1999 June 27; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 17)
  - Poets in the Park (2000-2002) posters, correspondence, sponsors, report, photographs, 2000 July 04; 2001 July 29; 2002 May 12; 2002 June 25 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 18)
  - Poetry Motel Foundation: community arts connection: calendar, interim report, correspondence, 1997 November 21-1998 June 15; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 19)
  - Poet Profiles and Information including Maurice Kenny, Lyn Lifshin, James Keller, 1982 April 09-1998 March 23; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 20)
  - Porter, Bern: photographs, posters, clippings, press releases, 1984 October 09; 1989 October-1989 November (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 21)
  - QE2 Halloween Poets' Open Mic Mark Smith 1995: clippings, poster, 1995 March 03; 1995 October 26; 1995 October 30; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 22)
  - Quincy Troupe at Livingston Middle School, 1991 October 18 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 21)
  - Readings 1986 editor (Drawer E3, Video-tape 22)
  - RAEW 1986 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 23)
  - RAEW: news clippings, 1984 April 23-1992 May 28 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 23)
  - RAEW: photo scrapbook 1, Undated (Box 10 (1-Events), Folder 1)
  - RAEW: photo scrapbook 2, Undated (Box 10 (1-Events), Folder 2)
  - RAEW: photo scrapbook 3, Undated (Box 10 (1-Events), Folder 3)
  - RAEW: phone bank lists, press releases, 1984 April 29-1997 April 29; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 24)
  - RAEW: reading pledges, press releases, 1984 April 29-1988 November 14; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 25)
  - RAEW: assorted materials: correspondence, clippings, readings schedule, 1985 April 29-1985 May 04; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 26)
  - RAEW and assorted events: clippings, calendar, press releases, 1985 May 03-1991 April 30; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 27)
  - RAEW: schedules, correspondence, clippings, minutes, 1989 January 19-1989 April 17; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 28)
  - RAEW: correspondence, materials, participants list, graphic design, fliers, 1986 March 18-1989 April 29; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 29)
  - RAEW 1987 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 24)
  - Readings 87 Tape 2, 1987 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 25)
  - Readings 87, #4, 1987 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 26)
  - RAEW #2, 1988 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 27)
  - RAEW #3, 1988 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 28)
  - RAEW #4, 1988 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 29)
  - RAEW #5, 1988 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 30)
  - RAEW #6, 1988 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 31)
  - RAEW #7, 1988 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 32)
  - RAEW #9, 1988 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 33)
  - RAEW 89 #1, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 34)
  - RAEW 89 #2, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 35)
  - RAEW 89 #3, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 36)
  - RAEW 89 #4, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 37)
  - RAEW 89 #5, children's hour, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 38)
  - RAEW 89 #6, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 39)
  - RAEW 89 #7, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 40)
  - RAEW 89 #8, 1989 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 41)
  - RAEW 90 #1, 1990 April 28 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 42)
  - RAEW 90 #2, 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 43)
  - RAEW 90 #3, 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 44)
  - RAEW 90 #4, 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 45)
  - RAEW 90 #5 10:15 am., 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 46)
  - RAEW 90 #6, 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 47)
  - RAEW 90 #7, 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 48)
  - RAEW 90 #8, 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 49)
  - RAEW end of, 1990 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 50)
  - RAEW 1990 Mailing (Drawer E3, Video-tape 51)
  - RAEW 91 #1, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 52)
  - RAEW 91 #2, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 53)
  - RAEW 91 #3, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 54)
  - RAEW 91 #4, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 55)
  - RAEW 91 #5, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 56)
  - RAEW 91 #6, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 57)
  - RAEW 91 #7, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 58)
  - RAEW 91 #9, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 59)
  - RAEW 91 #10, 1991 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 60)
  - RAEW 1992 poster, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - RAEW 1992 #1 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 61)
  - RAEW 1992 #2 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 62)
  - RAEW 1992 #3 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 63)
  - RAEW 1992 #4 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 64)
  - RAEW 1992 #5 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 65)
  - RAEW 1992 #6 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 66)
  - RAEW 1992 #7 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 67)
  - RAEW 1992 #8 (Drawer E3, Video-tape 68)
  - RAEW 1992 #9 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 69)
  - RAEW 1992 #10 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 70)
  - RAEW 1992 #11 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 71)
  - RAEW: endorsements, correspondence, clippings, 1987 January 20-1992 February 03; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 30)
  - RAEW: photographs, 1987 April-1987 May 21; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 31)
  - RAEW: poems, opening dedication, groundswell journal, 1987 Spring-1991 April 27; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 32)